### Aaron Zomback

Hello, I'm Aaron. I'm a software engineer and filmmaker. One of my goals is to transform and improve educational experiences through storytelling and immersive technology. I enjoy writing JavaScript, Ruby-on-Rails, Python, and Java to build a variety of full-stack needs.

3 Chemin de Gage Chazay-d'Azergues, France aaronzomback@protonmail.com +33 6 29 81 98 34



#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Freelance Software Developer and UX Designer Chazay d'Azergues, FR

March 2020 - present

I've been hired to work for a variety of successful clients, from designing a food takeout app for a start-up, a boutique t-shirt company, to redesigning a restaurant point-of-sale system. My portfolio can be found at www.zomback.design.

#### Sr. Research Associate Scientist, Calder Biosciences Brooklyn, NY

November 2014 - October 2019

Designed and conducted experiments targeting vaccine candidates for HIV, RSV (Respiratory Syncytial Virus) & Influenza.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### SuperHi, online courses

December 2019 - May 2020

Ruby-on-Rails, Foundations HTML/CSS/JavaScript, Command Line for Creatives, Intro to UX, Visual Design & Branding

#### University of Washington, Seattle, WA — Biochemistry B.S.

September 2009 - June 2014

Distinction: awarded Mary Gates Research Scholarship for host-virus research work, mentored by Dr. Matt Daugherty in the Malik Lab.

#### **SKILLS**

**CODING** Ruby on

Rails/Javascript/CSS/HTML/Git & GitHub foundational coding knowledge and applications.

UX/UI DESIGN Building interactive mobile/web prototypes in Figma. Other deliverables include: user-flows

VIDEO motion effects and graphics editing using Adobe After Effects. Expert with Adobe Premiere Cs6+

communication strong experience in working with clients to achieve their business goals. I have strong experience presenting scientific data, collaborating with other researchers and colleagues, & planning strategies to achieve business objectives.

VISUAL SOFTWARE
APPLICATIONS Figma, Framer,
Blender 3D, Illustrator,
Photoshop

#### **AWARDS**

Mary Gates Research Scholarship Viral & Host Protein Interaction Research

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

# Prefusion RSV F Immunization Elicits Th2-Mediated Lung Pathology in Mice

Eichinger, K.M., Kosanovich, J.L., Gidwani, S.V., **Zomback**, **A**., et al., Frontiers in Immunology, 29 July 2020

https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fimmu.2020.01673/full

### PROJECTS

#### TimeSink™ – A web app for an online cinema platform

Designing and developing an online platform for filmmakers to present their work and receive user reviews. I am writing the application using Ruby on Rails.

#### **FILMS**

#### Sovereign Blue - 2018, short film

My second short film that I created while I was living and working in Brooklyn, NY - I wrote, produced, and directed this short, featuring Rodney Ferrer as the maniacal CEO of a multi-media company. A review of the film can be found <a href="https://example.com/here">here</a> at UK Film Review.

#### Expanded Metal - 2016, short film

My first short film that I created. It later went on to screen at the 2017 Philip K. Dick Science Fiction film festival in New York City.

#### **LANGUAGES**

English (native), French (learning), Spanish (proficiency)